Callum Good

https://callum-good.github.io/



goodcc97@gmail.com 022 174 0465

Summary

Experienced back-end developer with roots in game development. Passion for learning and problem solving. A colourful background in previous jobs and experiences have allowed for a varied skill set and great development in soft skills.

Career History

Self contracted driver at Deliver Easy

Apr 2020 - Present

Student IT Adviser at Ask Otago

Feb 2019 – Jan 2020 (11 months)

Provided IT help to students. This was primarily face to face but occasionally over the phone or IM. Additional responsibilities included maintaining various computer labs across campus. This role allowed me to further improve both my people skills and general IT knowledge.

Retail/Reception at Pet Doctors

Mar 2017 - Feb 2018 (11 months)

The retail side included merchandising, serving customers, giving advice and information about animals and products, general cleaning and taking care of animals. Reception for the Vet Clinic included answering phones, booking appointments, relaying client requests with Vets and Vet nurses as well as charging bills. Situations were often very delicate with clients which helped me develop strong soft skills.

Retail Sales Assistant at Nichols Pet Centre

Mar 2016 - Mar 2017 (1 year)

Skills

C#, C++, ASP.NET Core, Laravel, Java, Networking, Git, PHP, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Vue.js, SQL, Git, Ruby, Python, Agile, Scrum

Education

Bachelor of Information Technology from Otago Polytechnic &

Southern Institute of Technology

Graduating Nov 2020

Achieved high grades and worked a lot in teams/groups. Gained experience in Networking, programming, web development, databases game development Linux, Security, Git and working with computer hardware.

Certificate of Information Technology (Level 4) from Otago

Polytechnic

Graduated 2018

National Certificate of Educational Achievement (level 3)

from Kavanagh College

Graduated 2015

References

Steve Dunn Team Administrator and Support Advisor, Student IT **Work phone:** 021 279 5171 - **Email:** steve.dunn@otago.ac.nz

Grayson Orr Lecturer at Otago Polytechnic

Work phone: 027 302 6129 - Email: graysono@op.ac.nz

Fiona Crutchley Manager at Pet Doctors

Phone: 027 324 9185 - Email: tl-thegardens@nzpetdoctors.co.nz

Anita Murphy Programme Manager for Undergraduate Studies (SIT)

Phone: +64 3-211-2699 - Email: Anita.Murphy@sit.ac.nz

Darren Clarke Director at Deals On Limited

Email: darren@clickstart.co.nz